Guide to the Computational Linguistics [videorecording]
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Computational linguistics [videorecording]
1987
V0360
American Association for Artificial Intelligence
Association for Computational Linguistics.
Gazdar, Gerald.
Linguistic Institute.
Linguistic Society of America.
Mellish, C. S., (Christopher S.), 1954-
Morgan Kaufmann Publishers..
Stanford University
1.32 Linear feet 22 videotapes (U-matic)
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Scope and Contents note
Twenty-two lectures of a full-length course on computational linguistics presented at the 1987 Linguistic Institute held at Stanford University.
Access Terms
Computational linguistics.
Collection Contents
- Part 1, 1987; 1.1; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 2, 1987; 1.2; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 3, 1987; 1.3; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 4, 1987; 1.4; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 5, 1987; 1.5; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 6, 1987; 1.6; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 7, 1987; 1.7; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 8, 1987; 1.8; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 9, 1987; 1.9; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 10, 1987; 1.10; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 11, 1987; 1.11; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 12, 1987; 1.12; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 13, 1987; 1.13; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 1)
- Part 14, 1987; 1.14; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 2)
- Part 15, 1987; 1.15; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 2)
- Part 16, 1987; 1.16; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 2)
- Part 17, 1987; 1.17; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 2)
- Part 18, 1987; 1.18; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 2)
- Part 19, 1987; 1.19; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 2)
- Part 20, 1987; 1.20; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 2)
- Part 21, 1987; 1.21; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 2)
- Part 22, 1987; 1.22; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 2)
Stamp description
San Mateo, CA :,Distributed by Morgan Kaufmann Publishers, Inc.,
General Note
Lecturers: Gerald Gazdar (University of Sussex) and Christopher Mellish (University of Edinburgh).
General Note
"Linguistic Institute Videotapes."